Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/susanne-toney-9a8b2910 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Research

Analysis

Teaching

Susanne Toney

Chairperson/Associate Professor, Center for Entrepreneurship Economics, Finance and Accounting at Hampton University Hampton

Summary

Experienced Chairperson and Associate Professor of Economics with a demonstrated history of leadership and service in higher education. Strong researcher and education professional skilled in Quality Teaching, Mentoring, Community Service, Public Speaking, Analytical Skills, and Data Analysis.

Experience

Hampton University
Chairperson/Associate Professor, Center for Entrepreneurship,
Economics, Finance and Accounting
August 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Hampton, Virginia

Savannah State University

7 years

Associate Professor Of Economics August 2017 - July 2019 (2 years) Savannah, Georgia Area

Assistant Professor of Economics August 2012 - July 2017 (5 years) Savannah, Georgia Area

Hampton University
Assistant Professor Of Economics
January 2005 - August 2012 (7 years 8 months)
Hampton, VA

Education

Jackson State University
Ph.D., Business Administration - Economics · (2001 - 2008)

Clark Atlanta University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Finance and Decision Sciences · (1995 - 2000)

Hampton University

Bachelor's Degree, Finance · (1984 - 1989)